A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, East Asia/Indochina, RG 3, Series 2 FA1481
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council records, East Asia/Indochina, RG 3, Series 2
1970, 1982-1994
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council
FA1481
21.24 Cubic Feet 46 letter-size document boxes and 8 legal-size document boxes.
Arrangement
The Social Science Research Council archives are arranged into three record groups distinguished by the date of their donation to the Archive Center. Accession 1 (Record Group 1) consists of the documents received by the Archive Center in 1990; Accession 2 (Record Group 2) was transferred to the Archive Center in 1994; Record Group 3 was transferred to the Archive Center in 2017-2018.
Within series the records are primarily arranged in original order.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Social Science Research Council records were donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center in 1990 and record transfers continue periodically. The records in this series were received in 2017-2018.
Biographical / Historical
The Social Science Research Council (SSRC) is a private, not-for-profit organization established in 1923 to advance research in the social sciences. The SSRC came into being through the initiatives of Wesley C. Mitchell and Charles E. Merriam, members of the American Political Science Association. Representatives of the American Economic Association, the American Sociological Society, the American Statistical Association, the American Historical Association and the American Psychological Association assisted Merriam and his associates in forming the SSRC. They invited the participation of other national associations in anthropology, history, and psychology, many of which designated representatives to the SSRC in the year following its incorporation on December 27, 1924.
To support its work, the SSRC turned not to the U.S. government, whose support seemed more appropriate for the natural sciences, but to private foundations. For the first fifty years, well over three-quarters of the SSRC's funding was provided by the Russell Sage Foundation, the Ford Foundation, the Carnegie Corporation, and two Rockefeller philanthropies, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial and the Rockefeller Foundation. By the 1970s, however, funds for some special projects were obtained from federal agencies.
Scope and Contents
The East Asia/Indochina series primarily contains records pertaining to the Indochina Studies Program (ISP), the Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), the Indochina Studies Committee, and related files. Files include: correspondence, papers and drafts, reports, periodicals, meeting records, grant files and fellows files.
Other Finding Aids
Other finding aids documenting Social Science Research Council records include:
FA021 Social Science Research Council records, Record Group 1 and Record Group 2 FA1196 Social Science Research Council records, Economics Intiative, RG 3, Series 1
- East Asia/Indochina, 1970, 1982-1994; 2
  - Indochina, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - ISEP Annual Report 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Concerned Citizen Newsletter - Nat'l League of Families of American Prisoners and Missing in Southeast Asia (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - SEASPAN - Northwest Regional Consortium, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam Confidentiel, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam Today, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vietnam Studies Bulletin, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Indochina Interchange Newsletter, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Asian Studies Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Association for Asian Studies - Khosana, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Newsletter, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin Signaletique C.I.D. Vietnam, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dow Jones News-Retrieval (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Indochina Digest, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Indochina Initiative, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Toward a new Vietnam (VN) proposal correspondence and notes (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Indochina Initiative - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - VLC Proposal Drafts, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ISEP Proposal notes and documents (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - ISEP Budget 1990, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ISEP Budget 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ISEP Future (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - USIA Materials to Incorporate (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - USIA Budgets (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - USIS Application (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - USIA drafts (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - USIA Appendices to No. 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - USIA Attachments (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - VNCSS Reform Workshop, 1990 June 27-30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Mary's Notes (Various) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Reception with SEASIA Scholars in Atlanta Area, 1990 March (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - US - Vietnam Courses Survey addresses (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - JCSEA-Cambodia (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ISEP Field Representatives Information (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Educational Exchange - ISEP (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ISEP Annual Report 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Stony Point Conference Information (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ISEP Fellowship Information '89-90, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Indochina Policy Forum File (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ISEP Friends (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ISEP Publicity (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - ISEP Committee Meeting, 1989 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - MBM's Japan Trip Sept. 1990, 1990 September (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - VNSOSCI printout (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - General SEA Information (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - SSRC-VCSS Economic Reform Workshop, 1990 June (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Indochina Clippings, 1992 April 9-May 21 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Indochina Clippings, 1990 November 26-1991 April 4 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - ISEP Committee Correspondence, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Vietnam-U.S. Relations Conference, Penn State, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Proposals (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bill Lobban Proposals (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - FEER Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Indochina Digest Clippings, 1991 September-1992 February (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Area Studies in Southeast Asia (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - William Lobban Project '93, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - IDC FEER (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Malaysia International Studies Program (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - IDC Economist (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Japan FEER (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Japan Economist (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Japan New York Times, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Japan Clippings, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Indochina Clippings, 1991 April (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Japan Clippings (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ISEP Committee Mailing June - 8 Nov (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Mary '91, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mary McDonnell - Japan, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Mary McDonnell - Japan Committee, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ISEP Program Announcements, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dee's ISEP Spring '91 Meeting Notes, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Grad. Students in Indochina (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - VCSS-SSRC Conference Volume, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - SSRC Computer Donation to Vietnam (VN), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Indochina Studies Program (ISP) Grantee List, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Indochina Studies Program (ISP) Grantee Publications Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Japan Program - Kathryn Ragsdale Dissertation, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Indochina Digest, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - China (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Turley Article (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Pro Bono Time (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Fellow Status Report Requests (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam Memos (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Japan - State of the Field (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - SSRC Publication Guidelines (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Indochina Background (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - ISEP - VCSS Workshop No. 1, 1990 June (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - ISEP - VCSS Workshop June '90, 1990 June (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - ISEP - Visit of Vietnam (VN) Economist, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - East-West Info. Center (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ISEP - Visit of Vietnam (VN) Librarian, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam Economic Reform Conference Papers, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Nguyen Manh Hung - ISP Fellow, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - JCSEA-ISEP 1989-90 Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - David Fetherman (DLF) Vietnam 1990 Trip File (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Mary McDonnell (MBM) 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Post-Reform Workshop 1990 File (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 2016:009:001 - McDonnell Book - Intact - Bound Volume (Box 8)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Special format items have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - McDonnell - Books in Vietnamese (Box 8)
  - McDonnell - The Vietnam Forum - Yale University, Southeast Asia Studies, Volumes 3, 4, 5, 6 and 8, 1984-1986 (Box 9)
  - McDonnell - The Vietnam Forum - Yale University, Southeast Asia Studies, Volumes 9, 11 and 12, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - McDonnell - Yale Center for International and Area Studies, Council on Southeast Asia Studies, The LAC-Viet Series, Volumes 1, 2, 8 and 9 (Box 10)
  - McDonnell - Books in Vietnamese (Box 11)
  - McDonnell - Laos: A Bibliography (Institute of Southeast Asian Studies), 1986 (Box 11)
  - McDonnell - Siang Bacthi: Tai Studies Center Publications #'s 1-5 (Box 11)
  - Vietnam on Filam and Television: Documentaries in the Library of Congress, Victoria E. Johnson, 1989 July (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - List of Publications - Indochina Studies Program (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Nancy Donnelly Publications "H'mong Batik" (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 2016:009:003 - H'mong Batik: A Textile Technique From Laos - Bound Volume (Box 12)
  - 2016:009:004 - H'mong Batik: A Textile Technique From Laos - Bound Volume (Box 12)
  - 2016:009:005 - H'mong Batik: A Textile Technique From Laos - Bound Volume (Box 12)
  - Nancy Donnelly's Dissertation (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Donnelly, Nancy Dissertation: The Changing Lives of Refugee Hmong Women (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 2016:009:002 - Mother of Writing - Bound Volume (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Lao Buddhist Customs: Courtship, Marriage Rites, Birth Rites in Pra Lak Pra Lam (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
  - The Vietnam Forum - Publications, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vietnamese Delegation - Notes, 1989 March (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Nguyen Xuan Oanh Meeting, 1988 October 12 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Visit to U.S. of Tran Chi Dao, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Indochina Advisory Group Meeting - Minutes, 1993 July 10 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam Courier, 1982-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Indochina Program - Participating Institutions (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP) Development, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - English as a Second Language, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Indochina Archive - 1985 - NYU, 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - French Contacts, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Vietnamese Delegation Visits, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Studies Program - Archiving - Microfilm Information, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SEA Resource Guide - Corrections (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SEA Resource Guide (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - SEA Resource Guide - Japan (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - SEA Resource Guide - Malaysia, Thailand, Indonesia (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Philippines (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - SEA Resource Guide - Canada (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - SEA Resource Guide - England, Italy, 1988-1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - SEA Resource Guide - France (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Univ. Catalogue requests for Indochina, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - SEA Resource Guide - Australia (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - SEA Resource Guide - Surveys and Memo (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - SEA Resource Guide - Netherlands (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Resources Guide Update - Corrections Made (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Resources Guide - Inquiries (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - SEA Resources Guide - Corrections Made for Foreign Guide (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Resources Guide Phase II (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Resources Guide - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE5 Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE20 John F. Kennedy Library, 1987-1992 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE7 Center for Vietnamese Studies, 1986-1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE3 Univ. of California at Berkeley. S-SEALS Collection, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE4 Genealogical Museum, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE8 University of Michigan, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE2 Cornell University Library Echols Collection, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE14 Hoover Institution Archives, 1987-1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE17 Stanford University Libraries, 1985-1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE21 Ohio University Libraries, 1987-1992 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE6 Dwight D. Eisenhower Library, 1986-1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - SURVE23 Cleveland Public Library, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE13 Arizona State University Libraries, 1987-1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE24 Columbia University Libraries, 1987-1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE19 University of Hawaii - Asia Collection, 1987-1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE16 Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, 1987-1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE10 Hoover Presidential Library, 1986-1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE15 Gerald R. Ford Library, 1986-1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - SEA Resources Guide (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - SEA Resources Survey, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE12 University of Wisconsin, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE22 Lyndon B. Johnson Library, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE1 Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1986-1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - SEA Resources Guide - Recipients, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - SEA Resources Survey Responses - Declinations, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Resources - Add. Funding (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - SURVE9 Harry S. Truman Library (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - SEA Resources Guide - SURVE Northern Illinois University - Hart Collection, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - SEA Resources Guide (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Conference Notes (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Toby Volkman - Conference Notes (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - East Asia Conference Reports and Journals, 1970, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Indochina Issues, 1985 October (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Colloquia, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Stony Point Conference - US-VN People to People Cooperation, 1989 December (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Carol Compton - Language Use and Language Policy, Hawaii, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - ISP Advisory Meeting, 1988 July 21 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Asilomar, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Lobban, William - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP) 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Ninh - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Pettus, Ashley - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Potkin, Alan - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Vasavakul, Thaveeporn - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Womack, Brantly - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - ISEP Fellowship General 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - ISEP Fellowship Chronological File, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - ISEP 1990-91 Fellowship Chronological File, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Dollar Scholars Form Letters (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Hunt, David - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Ledgerwood, Judy - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Mahoney, Therese M. - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 90-91, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - PPELIM. Appl. Country Breakdown '87, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 1986-1987-88 Summary Analysis of App. And Appl. Statistics, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - 1983-85 Summary Analyses of App. Applicant Statistics, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Inquiries for ISEP Competition, 1989 March (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Proposal Data List (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - April '88 Award Letters, 1988 April (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Interim Reports (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Interim Reports (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Awardees 1986-87, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Supplemental Awards (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1985-86 Awardees, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Copies of Grantee Face Sheets '83-'88, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Grantee Contact Addresses (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Grantee Award Packets Stage 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - March '89, April '89 - ISEP Committee Meeting (Agenda), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Centers' Meeting (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - ISP Committee Meeting Agenda 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Policy Forum Conference - Airlee House, 1988 October (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Performing Arts Workshop - Amy Catlin, UCLA, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Lobban, William - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 89-90, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Porter, Gareth - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Indochina Conferences, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Colloquia - Kinship and Gender, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dee - Tokyo (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - faxes from and to Dee (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Resource Guides - Post Completion Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lao Delegation Application - Application, Agreement and Financial (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Lao Delegation - Invitations and Logistics, 1988-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - JACIP - Committee Rosters and Awards, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - IAC - Joint Committee Agendas, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Joint Committees - Rosters, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - International Advisory Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - International Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - ISEP Publicity (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Program Publicity, 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Indochina Studies Program, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam Newsclippings - Economic Reform, 1980s (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Grantee Progress Report, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Kampuchea - Newsclippings, 1980s (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Bangkok Press Clips, 1989 January - February (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - ISEP Funding, 1990 Fall (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - United Board, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - ISEP Funding - MacArthur, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Phnom Penh, 1990 July (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Indochinese in the USA and Interested in ISEP (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Laos Proposal, 1988 Fall (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Info. For Lao, 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Laos Plans, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Laos - Reports and Agreements, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Laos - Pheuipanh, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Letter of Intent - Kampuchea, 1989 Spring (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Signed Letted of Intent - Cambodia, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Kampuchea Drafts (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Kampuchea Projects '89, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Chheng Phon, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Kampuchea Proposal Drafts, 1987 December (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Vietnam, 1989 Summer (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Mary McDonnell, 1989 July-August (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Kampuchea Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Laos Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - ISEP Committee Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Cambodia, 1989 May (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Vietnam (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Smith - Hefner, Nancy J., Indochina Studies Program (ISP) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Dai Lien Vo, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Han Tho Thouneh, ISP (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Khatharya UM, ISP, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Bunroeun Thach, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Kim Huot Kiet, ISP, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - SAM, Sam-Ang and Moly, ISEP, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Swearer, Donald, ISEP, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Ashmun, Lawrence F., ISEP, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Blumenthal, Eileen, ISEP, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Diffloth, Gerard ISEP, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Duiker, William J. ISEP, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Amis Lyman, ISP, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Sim Um, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Duc X. Nguyen, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Ken Erickson, ISP (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Joseph Helmick, ISP (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Richard Adicks, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - George Boeck, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Bounhong Khomarath, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Linda Crum, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Murial Paskin Carrison, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Thai Ba Nguyen, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Nguyen Dinh Nghia, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Marsha McDowell, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Insuon, ISP, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Prince Chandetka, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - William Taylor Smathers, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - David T. Lee, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - David Kopf, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Mong Hap Lao, ISP, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Tren Tuong Nhu, ISP, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sarom Prien, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Adelaida Reyes Schramm, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Srila Sen, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Donald J. Wilcox, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Tam Dang Wei, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Judie Telfer, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Tran Van An, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Nguyen Van Ahn, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Nguyen Van Hahn, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Nguyen Van Loc, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Tam Thanh Phan, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Paul J. Rutledge, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Barbara Alice Frye, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Lorraine Majka, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Giebal, Lessard, Mchale, Montesano, Zinoman, ISEP, 1989 - 1990 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Proschan, Tayanin, ISEP, 1989 - 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Poc, Thieun Lo, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Meriam Lobel, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Ros Chantrasot, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Steven C. Moore, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Nguyen, Minh P., ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Phon-Ahn Nquyen, ISP, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Pheng Kol, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Kim Huot Kiet, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Charles R. Lee, ISP, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 10)